cocland.com 2019-07-23

# Privacy Policy | Clash of Clans Land

**Cookies** :

We don’t use cookies.

**Visitor Stats** :

We are using [Google Analytics](http://www.google.com/analytics/) to improve and optimize our website. You can read more of its privacy policies at Google Analytics website!

**Ad Networks**

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies

We use the following ad networks:

  * Google Adsense ([Privacy Policy](http://www.google.com/privacy.html))

**Especially Google Adsense Privacy Policy**

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site.
  * Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our sites and other sites on the Internet.
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other use

**Contacting Us:**

If you have any questions, you can contact me at: <https://cocland.com/about>

This website uses cookies to improve your experience. We'll assume you're ok with this, but you can opt-out if you wish.Accept [Read More](https://cocland.com/)
